

PERSONAL PROFILE

Born in Jakarta, June 19, 1997, I became interested in audiovisual when I was a child. Decided go to multimedia school in Vocational High School. Joined the film community & made short film debut as an assistant writer **PHOBIA** in 2014.

I also create a film community at university, and produce film and video content. Several films won awards such as Official Selection at the 2018 SCTV Indonesia Short Film Festival for the film BUNGA and Viddsee Audience Choice Award 2021 for the film HARI SUDAH PETANG.

For me, films are not just ordinary audio-visual works. More than that, film is a communication message that involves ideas, feelings and experiences that are packaged in the most complete aesthetics of art so as to make anyone who sees it can feel it.

CAREER SUMMARY

Video Director - Marketing Communication 2020-2021 | Sekai Home

Video Editor - Production Team 2021-Present | Hill+Knowlton Strategies

Video Director - Creative Development 2022-Present | Growth Center - Kompas Gramedia

AWARDS

2014 - Devendra Fest 2014 | PHOBIA | BEST STORY

2015 - Sonic Linguistic 2015 | OTW | 3RD PLACE WINNER

2017 - FISIP Folk Fest | BUNGA | BEST FILM

- FISIP Ethnic Fest 2017 | BUNGA | BEST FILM

2018 - ISFF SCTV 2018 | BUNGA | OFFICIAL SELECTION

2020 - Genflix Film Fest | AKUT | OFFICIAL SELECTION

- Genflix Film Fest | PBP | OFFICIAL SELECTION

- Ministry Social Film Fest | MKTNNBA | OFFICIAL SELECTION

2021 - Bogor Indie Film Fest | BARU TAU | OFFICIAL SELECTION

- Viddsse ACA 2021 | Hari Sudah Petang | OFFICIAL SELECTION

EDUCATION

MULTIMEDIA SCHOOL 2012 - 2015 | SMK Bhakti Anindya Tangerang

FACULTY OF COMMUNICATION

2017 - 2021 | Muhammadiyah Tangerang University

CORE SKILLS

Concepting

Script Writing

Wisual Thinking

Concepting

Wisual Thinking

Concepting

Conc

FILMOGRAPHY

•	PHOBIA Co Writer	2014
•	OTW Writer & Director	2015
•	BUNGA Writer & Director	2017
•	AKUT Writer & Director	2018
•	PERMEN BUAT PELANGI Writer & Director	2019
•	MKTNNBA Writer & Director	2020
•	BARU TAU Creative Producer	2021
•	HARI SUDAH PETANG Director	2021

CONTACTS

Karawaci, Kota Tangerang.

aldio.bagaskara@gmail.com

(aldbgskr

0859 4539 7730



Portofolio Site